Guide to the Jim Fouratt Papers
Fouratt (Jim) Papers
- Band demos and recordings, 1980 1989; Series IV; 77.42 Linear Feet; (78 boxes); 1347 Audiocassettes; 7 Audiotape Reels
  - Ausdruckstanz, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023748)
  - Johnny Reno & The Sax Maniacs, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023755)
  - Blitz Girls, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023763)
  - Nicolas Collins - Devil Music, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:27:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023771)
  - Philip Glass - The Photographer, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:42:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023789)
  - Christmas Four Song Demo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950453)
  - Fetchin Bones, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950370)
  - Jesse Malin and Hope, 1986; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950529)
  - Measure of Disorder, 1985; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950511)
  - White Noise, 1985 October; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950503)
  - Xotika, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950495)
  - The Dance, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950487)
  - "t instruments", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950479)
  - Mudd Puppies, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950461)
  - Lonesome Val, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950446)
  - Michael Gordon, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950438)
  - The Wygals, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950420)
  - Antietam, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950412)
  - Tiny Lights, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950404)
  - Raw Youth, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:39:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140908378)
  - Don King, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950396)
  - Angela Bowie, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 94, Item barcode 39002140950388)
  - Javelosa, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218526)
  - The Slickaphonics, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218518)
  - Miller, Miller, Miller + Sloan, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218500)
  - Polyrock, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218492)
  - Judy Nylon, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:39:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218484)
  - Terminal, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218476)
  - Sleepers, Factrix, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:08:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218468)
  - Civil Wars, Rome, 1984 March 25; 1 Audiocassette; 01:32:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218450)
  - Wanda the Way It Is, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218443)
  - Bond Bergland Solo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:47:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is silent from 11:12-14:43, then unrelated content until the end of the tape. Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218435)
  - Arms Akimbo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218427)
  - Vamos Ganando La Paz, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:38:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218419)
  - Tanzplagen, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218401)
  - Eye and I (Melvin Gibbs and D.K. Dyson), 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The song repeats for the last eight minutes of the program and ends abruptly. Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218393)
  - Roni & The Jittrs, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:03:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218385)
  - Science, 1985 June; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218377)
  - Swimming Pool Q's, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 95, Item barcode 39002137218369)
  - New Math Mechanical Servants, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:25:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903825)
  - Dancing Hoods, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903833)
  - Tirez Tirez, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:25:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903841)
  - Helen Wheels Band, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. An echo, at times, can be heard on the audio. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903858)
  - Von LMO, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903866)
  - Satin Latins, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903494)
  - George Wrage Group, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903874)
  - The Method Actors - Round World, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903882)
  - Transfactor, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903890)
  - The Cosmopolitans, 1982; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903908)
  - Units, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The volume drops in the left channel from 00:05:07-00:05:10. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903916)
  - Siren, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903924)
  - Los Microwaves, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; This tape will not play. It has not been digitized. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903932)
  - Transfactor, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903940)
  - Fade to Black - Corridors of Gender, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903957)
  - Vivid Section, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:54 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static and dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903965)
  - Of a Mesh, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903981)
  - The Folk Brothers, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 96, Item barcode 39002140903973)
  - WKGB, 1978; 1 Audiocassette; 00:27:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968158)
  - The Dance - In Lust, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:48:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968166)
  - Lou Miami & The Kozmetix, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:05:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); An echo, at times, can be heard on the program. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968174)
  - TBA, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968182)
  - Sirens - BG, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968190)
  - Funkapolitan, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968208)
  - The Wallets, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:27 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968216)
  - Suburbs demo, 1979 May 1; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968224)
  - Uranus #1, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:27:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968232)
  - Vic Varney, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:39:26 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968240)
  - Jean Caffeine, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968257)
  - Velveteen, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); An echo can be heard, at times, in the program. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968265)
  - They Might Be Giants, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140966996)
  - Sing Sing, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968273)
  - The X-Men - Dead Man's T.V., 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968307)
  - Bebe Buell, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968299)
  - True Romance, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 97, Item barcode 39002140968281)
  - False Prophets, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952277)
  - Binky Philips - On, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952269)
  - Revelons, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952251)
  - Suzanne Vega, 1985 March 10; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952244)
  - Yo La Tengo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952236)
  - Nora York, 1986; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952228)
  - Die Fake Germans, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952210)
  - Midnight Walkers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952202)
  - Cowboy Mouth, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952194)
  - The Microscopic Septet, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952186)
  - Absolute Elsewhere, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952178)
  - Barbara Ess, 1982 February 21; 1 Audiocassette; 00:34:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. This is a separate recording from the same Barbara Ess performance on February 21st, 1982 documented in this collection. This sound of this recording is clearer. (Box 98, Item barcode 39002141020736)
  - Eel Dogs, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952160)
  - Shöx Lumania, 1981; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952152)
  - Murray Elias (AKA Jah Fish), 1980 November 22; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952145)
  - UT, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 98, Item barcode 39002141025669)
  - Y Pants, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 98, Item barcode 39002140952137)
  - Dreams So Real, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:28:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static and dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022609)
  - 3 Teens Kill 4 - No Motive, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static and dropouts are present in the audio. There is a buzz in the program. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022591)
    Songs include "Dishes", "Falling Out", "Special Reserve", and "Too Much Too Soon".
  - 3 Teens Kill 4 - No Motive, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:30:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static and dropouts are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022583)
    Songs include "Visitation", "Tell Me Something Good", "Hut", "Bean Song", "5/4", "Crime Drama", "Hunger - pt. 2", and "Hunger".
  - Mikel Rouse (Tirez Tirez) - Story of the Year, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:45:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022575)
  - 3 Teens Kill 4, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022567)
    Songs include "No Motive", "3 Teens", "Hold Up", and "Visitation".
  - 3 Teens Kill 4, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); There is a warble in the audio. Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022559)
    Songs include "Falling Out" and "Place to Hide".
  - Linda Hudes Power Trio - Century XXI, Antigua, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022542)
  - The Scientific Americans, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022534)
  - George Wrage, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022526)
  - Tiny Desk Unit, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022518)
  - The Modern Rage, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022500)
  - 30° Lubna, 1985 March 13; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022492)
  - Rubber Rodeo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:17:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022484)
  - The Misfits, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio hiss and hum are present. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022047)
  - Helen Wheels Band, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); There is a warble in the audio. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022476)
  - Ultraviolence, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. High amounts of buzz and dropouts in the audio. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022468)
  - "Figures Øn Ȧ Beach", 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. High amounts of hum are present. (Box 99, Item barcode 39002141022450)
  - Avedon, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218534)
  - Los Microwaves, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:56:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218542)
  - Mark Oliver, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 0:32:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218559)
  - "RocKids", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218567)
  - Red Crayola, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218575)
  - Coté Coté, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio is low. Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218583)
  - Noise "R" Us, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218591)
  - Mikata demo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:41:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218609)
  - The Cucumbers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:36:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218617)
  - Hüsker Dü - We Wish You A Merry Christmas, 1986; 1 Audiocassette; 00:01:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218625)
  - Natural Enemies, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:41:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218633)
  - Dream Syndicate, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:47:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218641)
  - The Therapy Sisters, 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:42:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218658)
  - Peter Blue and the Girlfriends, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218666)
  - Ornette Coleman - Don't You Know, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218674)
  - She, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218682)
  - Comateens, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. Low and high-frequency speed fluctuations are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218690)
  - "+ INSTRUMENTS", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002137218708)
  - Joe Rudick DJ, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:31:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907867)
  - The X-Men, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the program are present. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907875)
  - Bound + Gagged, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio is distorted. Audio hiss and hum are present. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140905465)
  - Bound + Gagged, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are heard. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140905473)
  - Kongress, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907883)
  - The Leisure Units, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:19:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907891)
  - Human Switchboard, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the program are present. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907909)
  - Basics, 1980 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:27:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Droputs in the program can be heard. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907917)
  - Kongress, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907925)
  - Circus Mort, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002137159464)
  - MX-80, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:32:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static, clicks, and pops are present. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907933)
  - Insect Surfers, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 01:00:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static, clicks, and pops are preent. There is a warble in the audio. Dropouts are present. Speed fluctuations can be heard. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907941)
  - Laura Logic, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:45:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static and dropouts in the audio are present. The program is in silence from 00:43:04-00:43:37. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907958)
  - Bang Zoom, Shop Assistants, Pastels, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:32:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static, clicks, and pops are present. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907966)
  - Trigger & Her Thrill Kings, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 101, Item barcode 39002140907974)